KDK-12  听到请回答
KDK-12, come in.
呼叫KDK-12
KDK-12.
这里是KDK-12
波比  需要你顺道去佩可迪瓦女士那里查看一下
Hey, Bobby, need you to look in on Mrs. Peyketewa.
她没事吧
She all right?
她女儿从加利福尼亚打电话回来
Her daughter called from California,
说已经很久都无法和她取得联系了
she hasn't heard from her in a while,
有点担心
kind of worried.
这就去
Will do.
佩可迪瓦女士  你在家吗
Miss Peyketewa, hello.
佩可迪瓦女士
Miss Peyketewa.
Peyketewa女士
这里是KDK-12
KDK-12 here.
珍妮特  老天
Janet, Jesus,
能再说一遍吗
Come again?
是佩可迪瓦女士  她被人杀了
Miss Peyketewa, she's dead.
我这里需要些支援
I need some backup out here.
好的  马上就到
Ok. On their way.
里面的人  马上出来
Whoever's in there, show yourself right now.
站那别动  把手举起来
Hold it right there! Let me see your hands.
把手举起来
Hands!
好了  跪下  跪在地上
All right, down. On your knees.
你能听懂我说的吗  你懂英语么
You understand me? Do you speak English?
我说跪下  快给我跪下
I said down! On your knees. Down!
他妈的  给我跪下  跪下
Damn it, get down! On your knees!
快点
Do it!
快跪下  否则我就开枪了
On your knees or I'll fire!
绝
命
毒
师
第三季
第六集
是我
Yeah.
我找到文件了
I found the papers.
就在你放它们的储物箱里
Right where you left them, in the crib.
是的  好吧
Yeah, well...
你最了解了  对吗
you know best, right?
还有什么要说的吗
Anything else?
你有想过我们该怎样
Do you have any thought about
和小沃尔特解释这事吗
how we're going to approach this with Walter Jr?
他还是我儿子  我是说  他依然
Well, he's still my son. I mean, he will remain--
当然了
Of course.
我说的是离婚这件事
My point being the divorce.
我想他能够理解的  不是吗
Well, I-- I think he gets it. Don't you?
我是说  我想他知道会有这么一天的
I mean, I-- I think he saw it coming.
他看得出你的痛苦还有
He sees your unhappiness and--
我的痛苦
My unhappiness?
我完全不守贞操  罪有应得的痛苦吗
My completely out-of-the-clear, blue-sky unhappiness?
是吗
Really?
听着  就像你说的  出于好意而已
Look, as you said, for the best.
是
Yeah.
好吧  最后一件事
Okay, um, last thing,
之后就不打扰你了
and then I'll let you go.
在儿童抚养表里
In the Child Support Worksheet,
你列出了医疗  牙医  儿童护理
you list medical, dental, child care,
交通  购房  教育  食品  衣物
transportation, housing, education, food, clothing.
是的  全部
That's right, all of it.
沃尔特  不行
Walt... no.
斯凯勒  你想让我离开家  我离开了
Skyler, you wanted me out, I'm out,
但我会为我的家人提供生活保障
but I will provide for my family.
但不能用那种钱
Not with that money.
你这是在犯罪后还让我们也变成帮凶
You'd be making us accessories after the fact.
斯凯勒  那你以为过去的半年里
Skyler, how do you think we've been
我们的账单都是怎么付的
paying our bills these last six months?
我得挂了
I have to go.
是  我猜的没错
Yep, I was right.
有三套房是空着的
Three units available,
都是完全相同的建筑的平面图
exact same floor plan.
如果你愿意的话
I can call over,
我还可以带你去看看其他的房间
get you in to see any of the others if you'd like.
不用了  这间就挺好的
No. No, this one's fine.
就买这间了
I'll take it.
不巧的是  这是一个样板间  所以
Now, unfortunately, this one is the model, so--
是的  我很喜欢
Yeah, I like it.
我喜欢这里的一切
I like everything about it.
就原样买下了
I'll-- I'll take it as is.
在这个世界上还有什么不能交易的东西吗
Name one thing in this world that is not negotiable.
哦  老天  你得清理一下油锅
Oh, Jesus. You have to clean the fryer.
是的  先生
Yes, Sir.
我们每晚都会尽力去清理它们
So we try to clean them every night,
不过在你打开进气阀之前
but make sure it's off
请先确保它是关着的
before you open the intake valve.
很好
Good.
我建议你把这个任务也添加到
Now, I suggest that you add this
你周一的维修任务清单里
to your Monday maintenance schedule.
是的  先生
Yes, sir.
现在选择冷冻模式  关掉小按钮
Now select freezing mode and micro button off,
摁下"完成前操纵等待"
pressing "hold other control until it beeps".
主阀门开  主开关开
Main valve on, main switch on.
指针指向绿色前压缩机需要先运行一会
Give the compressor time for the needle to enter the green.
你来真的啊  这全是你做的
You're for real. This is all you?
独自做的
All me.
管他个鸟海森堡  你知道我在说什么
Heisenberg who? That's what I say.
我兄弟杰西也可以制
My man Jesse can cook.
快看  毫无浑浊
Check it, yo. It ain't cloudy
毫无杂质  浑然天成
or dirty or nothing.
只有完美的纯蓝色泽
Just the right shade of blue.
完美的色泽
Good shade.
看看那个水晶块的个头
Check out that crystal size, yo.
这家伙要是再大点
If that bitch was any bigger,
就是巧丽兰了[糖果品牌]
it would be a Jolly Rancher.
别客气
Be my guest.
你确定吗
You sure?
我觉得恢复期里的你看上去帅呆了
I feel kind of diggish with you being in rehab and all.
没错  我一直留意时局
No. I can watch, yo.
一边制毒  一边留意时局
I can cook, and I can watch.
试一下吧  我上周的时候试过了
Go for it. I tried it, like, last week.
我的兴奋劲还没过去呢
I'm still coming down.
慢慢来
Go easy.
好吧
Okay.
哇哦  大河之舞
Whoo! Riverdance!
嘿  别踢我地板了  笨蛋  赶紧的
Hey-- Hey, stop marking up my floor, dumbass. Come on.
来向我鞠躬吧
Bow before me.
我就是舞蹈之王  对吗
I am Lord of the Dance. Huh?
他妈的  我得再吸一口试试
Shit. I gotta try that again.
别了  我觉得你可以了
Uh, yeah, no, I think you're good.
真是太爽了  杰西
That is awesome, Jesse.
感觉就像有人把我的大脑拿走
I feel like somebody took my brain out
然后放在沸水中去煮一样
and boiled it in, like, boiling hot--
说真的  老兄  这简直太棒了
It's the bomb, man, seriously.
简直就像是炭疽
Like-- like anthrax.
很好
Good.
那...你们想谈点生意了吗
So, um... you ready to talk some business?
你是说  这不只是在消遣吗
You mean, this is not, like, just... recreational?
我知道你们在想什么
I know what you're thinking.
相信我  不会再和以前一样了
Trust me. It's not going to be like it was--
好吗  永远都不会和以前一样了
All right, never gonna be like it was.
那怎么可能
How's that?
我们只在安全的情况下才卖掉它
We sell it safe.
好吗  我们聪明点去卖掉它
All right? We sell it smart.
我们不要像之前那样贪婪了
We don't get greedy... like before.
我不知道  老兄
I don't know, man.
康宝他们
Combo and all.
还是老样子
Still.
大家都得生存
Man's gotta make his living.
如果能像杰西说的那样
If it's like Jesse says
我们不再贪婪
and we're not greedy...
我是说  我想是能成功的
I mean, I guess I can see it.
在我们开始碰运气之前
Had a good thing going
好事情就已经发生了
before we started pushing our luck.
是的
Yeah.
如果能做到那样个子的话
If it can go back to being like that and all--
嘿 肯定会的
Hey, it will be.
首先  我们编制一个存货清单
Step 1-- we build inventory.
猴子  去找克洛维斯
Badger, go see Clovis.
把房车开到隐蔽的地方
Get the RV in shape,
整修一下  润滑油
tune up, oil change,
刹车灯  之类的东西
brake lights, and whatnot.
警察总是因为刹车灯让你靠边停下
Cops always pull you over for brake lights.
不能是我们
Not us.
谨慎小心
Cautious.
-我知道  -没问题
- I know. - You got it.
好了  你知道那个警报器吧
All right, you know that buzzer thing.
在点火时拔掉钥匙
Leave the key in the ignition,
它就会响  无所谓了
and it buzzes, whatever.
-是的  -让他给也装上一个那东西
- Yeah. - Just have him put in one of those, too.
瘦子你来负责供给
Skinny, you're in charge of supplies.
我会给你列个清单
I'll get you a list.
听你差遣
Right on.
行吗
Yeah?
-行  -那这事定了
- Yeah. - All right.
那么  我们说好了
So, uh... we good?
-嗯  -没问题吧
- Yeah. - We good?
-挺你  伙计  -那就定了
- Right on, man. - All right.
我们干它一票
Let's do this thing.
布兰登·梅休
Brandon Mayhew.
我知道你的好事
I know you.
阿尔布开克真小啊
Small world, Albuquerque.
想要谈一下吗
Want to talk about it?
有什么好谈的  我没有发言权
Why? It's not like I get a vote.
你知道吗  讽刺得很
You know, ironically,
我想  从今往后  你会更加更加了解我这个人
I think you're going to see much more of me from now on.
-当然  -至少可以看到我真实的一面
- Sure. - Well, just as much of me at least.
我送你去学校  接你回来  以后天天如此
I'm taking you to the school, to and from, every day.
怎么  这事我也没发言权吗
What, I don't get a vote in this, either?
就因为你心存愧疚
I gotta stop going with Louis
我就不能跟路易斯上下学了吗
just because you're feeling guilty?
我是心存愧疚
I do feel guilty.
我就是这么一个人  孩子
I am the man that I am, son,
有许多地方我会改进  但是
and there's plenty I would change about that, but...
事已至此
here we are
你要接受现实
and this is just what it is.
知道么
You know what?
当我疯了吧
Call me crazy,
但我打心里觉得未来非常美好
but I'm actually feeling very good about the future.
早啊
Morning.
他们又回来了
They're back.
我就是在想
Uh, I'm just wondering
我们是否应该报警之类的
if we should maybe call the police or something.
为什么
Why?
他们又没干坏事
They're doing nothing wrong.
好了  把这个摆到三十三号桌  行吗
Okay, let's put this on table 33, okay?
你好  这位先生
Hello, there.
你是怀特先生  对吗
Uh, Mr. White, I presume?
噢  是的  你好  真是...对不起
Oh, yes. Hi. I am-- Sorry.
我马上下来
I'll-- I'll be right down.
你好  我是盖尔·伯蒂彻
Hi. Gale Boetticher.
你好
Hi.
你是我新的实验助手  我猜想
You're my new lab assistant, I take it.
是的  我是
Yes, I am.
我觉得你会想要了解一下我的资质
I suppose you'll want to hear my qualifications.
我带来了我的简历  在这儿
I have my, uh-- my resume here for you.
我在新墨西哥大学拿到学士学位
I received my bachelor's degree from UNM,
研究生学位是在科罗拉多州大学
my master's from the University of Colorado.
有机化学系  专攻...
Organic chemistry with a specialty in--
都写在上面
It's all right there.
X射线结晶学
"X-ray crystallography."
是真的么
Really?
这玩意儿我可以连续说上好几个小时
I could talk about that for hours.
我愿意听你讲
I would love to.
但是  首先  我好奇这是什么
But, first, I'm curious about this.
这是我最喜爱的一个小项目
That's a little pet project of mine.
你看  我认为
See, in my opinion,
这全在于奎宁酸含量
it's all about the quinic acid level.
假设只想要每升提取四千八百毫克
You want just north of 4,800 milligrams per liter,
但是如果烧煮过度
but if you over-boil to get there,
丹宁酸会被滤掉
you're going to leach your tannins.
苦味跑了  难喝
Bitterness. Yuck.
所以  我给它抽了真空
So I pull a mild vacuum.
这样  我就可以把温度
That way, I can keep the temperature
控制在九十二摄氏度以内  还有...
no higher than 92 C, and uh...
我给你弄点儿
let's see.
由你自个儿来评判
Judge for yourself.
天哪
Oh, my God.
这是我喝过的最美味的咖啡
My God, that is the best coffee I've ever tasted.
苏门答腊岛的咖啡豆
Sumatran beans,
研磨的功夫也了得
and I also have to give credit to the grind,
总之  谢谢夸奖  怀特先生
but, uh, thank you, Mr. White.
沃尔特
Walt, please.
请叫我沃尔特
Call me Walt.
我们干吗还用得着制毒呢
Huh, why the hell are we making meth?
告诉我  用苯乙酸溶液
Tell me, with the phenylacetic acid solution,
你说过前十分钟是每分钟一百五十滴
you said 150 drops per minute for the first 10 minutes,
然后剩下的每分钟九十滴
and then 90 for the remainder.
这是为什么呢
Why is that?
我的想法是
Well, my thinking is,
通过逐渐减少苯基
by tapering the phenyl,
得到的涵水层更具油性  于是
you get an oilier aqueous layer, and hence--
苯的萃取物会更好
Better benzene extraction.
说得很对
Exactly.
不过我其实更倾向于乙醚
But actually I prefer ether.
噢  我明天用它试试
Oh. I'll have it for tomorrow.
盖尔  我在想  你是怎么...
Gale, I'm wondering how you--
沦落至此的
Ended up here.
尽管实际上  我还没想出来
Well, actually, I'm still wondering
我到底是怎么沦落到这儿的  但是  你呢
how I ended up here, but, yes.
我是说  我无法想象
I mean, I can't imagine
我俩锒铛入狱互殴的景象
we strike each other as criminals.
因为犯罪  所以犯罪
Well, there's crime, and then there's crime,
我这么认为
I suppose.
我是个绝对的自由意志论者
I'm definitely a libertarian.
赞成成年人的观点  想他们所想
Consenting adults want what they want,
况且即便我不提供帮助
and if I'm not supplying it,
他们也能找到别人
they will get it somewhere else.
可至少在我这里
At least with me,
他们肯定会物超所值
they're getting exactly what they pay for.
无杂质  不掺假
No added toxins or adulterants.
我曾经过着与自己身份相配的生活
Yeah, I was doing it the way you are supposed to,
在科大攻读博士学位
pursuing my doctorate at Colorado,
参与美国国家卫生基金会项目
NSF research grant.
我也曾得意一时
I was on my way,
做得比别人多  也受人器重
jumping through hoops, kissing the proper behinds,
专注于所有非化学的事情
attending to all the non-chemistry
搞得自己焦头烂额
that one finds oneself occupied with.
你了解那个圈子
You know that world.
那才不是我要的生活
That is not what I signed on for.
我喜欢实验室
I love the lab.
因为这里充满魔力
Because it's all still magic.
你明白吗
You know?
化学
Chemistry?
我的意思是  一旦失去那种...
I mean, once you lose that...
确实是  这里是有魔力的地方
It is. It is magic.
现在依然如此
It still is.
从始至终我脑子里不断回想着
And all the while I kept thinking
那个伟大的老诗人惠特曼
about that great, old Whitman poem.
"当我聆听那位博学的天文学家讲座时"
"When I Heard the Learn'd Astronomer."
沃尔特·惠特曼
Walt Whitman.
我,,,我不知道这首诗
I-- I don't know it.
那算了吧
Uh, anyway...
你能朗诵它吗
Well, can you recite it?
可悲得很  我能
Pathetically enough I could.
好呀  那你念来听听吧
All right, well...
别不好意思  念吧  念吧
No, no, come on. Come on.
我真念了
Yeah?
"当我聆听那位博学的天文学家讲座时
When I heard the learn'd astronomer;
当那些证明  数据一栏栏地
When the proofs, the figures,
排列在我眼前时
were ranged in columns before me;
当那些表格  图解展现在我眼前
When I was shown the charts and the diagrams,
要我去加  去减  去测定时
to add, divide, and measure them;
当我端坐聆听那位天文学家的演说
When I, sitting, heard the astronomer,
听着演说室里此起彼伏的掌声时
where he lectured with much applause in the lecture-room,
我竟莫名其妙的厌倦起来
How soon, unaccountable, I became tired and sick;
于是我起身悄悄地溜了出去
Till rising and gliding out,
在神秘而潮湿的夜风中
I wander'd off by myself,
踯躅前行
In the mystical moist night-air,
一遍又一遍
and from time to time,
在姣彻的寂静中仰望星空"
Look'd up in perfect silence at the stars.
我承认  我是个书呆子
Yes, I am a nerd.
-太精彩了  -谢谢你
- Bravo. - Thank you.
来呀  平克曼
Come on, Pinkman.
你个鼠辈混球
You little rat busters.
别懒在屋子里  出来犯犯法
Get off your lazy ass and go break the law.
嘿  亲爱的
Hey, baby.
你还要不要回家了
Are you ever coming home?
玛丽  我在工作  行吗
Marie, I'm working. All right?
找到那辆房车了吗
Did you find it? The RV?
没  还在找
Nope. Working on it, so...
为什么不能直接逮捕他
Why can't you just arrest him,
逼他招呢
make him tell you?
宝贝儿  这事没那么简单
It's not that simple, baby.
有个东西叫宪法的
There's a little thing called The Constitution.
宪法...
The Constitution...
我对天发誓  我真想把这小崽子...
This kid, I swear to God, I wish I just could...
是那个叫平克曼的吗
This is that Pinkman character?
就是他
That's the one.
我能肯定那辆房车是他的
Positive the little bastard has got an RV,
只是不知道他藏在哪里
and I just don't know where he keeps it.
只能等他自己露出马脚
Until he actually leads me to where...
我陷在这儿了  玛丽
or does something, I'm stuck here, Marie,
对不起
so... sorry.
那...不是旧事重提
Well, um... not to bring up ancient history,
我只是想到一个人  他可能会了解
but I for one can think of someone who might know something...
一点情况
possibly.
值得一试
It's worth a shot.
是吗
Yeah?
谁
Who?
《草叶集》  沃尔特·惠特曼 著
喂
Hello.
喂  老兄  你好  最近怎么样
Oh, hey, buddy. Hey, how you doing?
汉克  什么事
Oh, hey, Hank. What's up?
我不想打扰你
Listen, I hate to bother you.
只是...只问你一个问题
I just... I just, uh... I just have a quick question.
说吧
Oh, shoot.
我现在实在是  走投无路了
Now, I'm only asking you this because I'm at a, you know,
所以才求救于你
dead-end here potentially.
我在查一个案子
I'm working a case, and, uh...
听我说  你要知道  我是最不愿意
Listen, you gotta know that I would never put you on the spot
让你尴尬为难的
or make you uncomfortable.
汉克  有话直说吧
Hank, you could just cut to the chase.
当年你失踪了
Back when we lost you
我到处找你的时候
and I was trying to track you down
找到你以前的一个学生  杰西·平克曼
through a former student of yours, Jesse Pinkman,
向你交个底  我知道
now, you know that I know
当初你可能跟他买过大麻
that once upon a time he may have dealt you a little weed.
汉克
Hank...
一点点而已  我不介意
Just a little, and I so do not care about that.
据我所知  你从没吸过  好吧
As far as I'm concerned, you never inhaled, okay?
照你的意思  我们有话直说
Like you said, cut to the chase.
你记不记得平克曼这小子有辆房车
Do you remember if this Pinkman kid ever had an RV?
就是休闲车
You know, a recreational vehicle,
温尼贝戈那种款式
you know, like a Winnebago-type deal,
棕黄条纹的
brown and beige?
问这干嘛
Uh, why?
这可说来话长
Well, it's a long story,
总之据我分析
but I'm personally of the opinion
他现在不贩大麻
that he's moved on from weed
直接卖晶体冰毒了
and graduated to selling crystal meth,
那房车就是他的移动实验室
using it as a rolling lab.
沃尔特
Walt?
唷
Yo.
说话呀  怀特老师
What? Mr. White.
喂  我的大天才忙什么呢
Hey, how's my favorite genius?
这电话安全吗
Is this a secure line?
Is this a secure...
自然  你怎么...
Yes, what's with the...
你也好啊
Hey, hello to you, too.
我们有麻烦了  毒管局找上门了
Listen, we've got a problem, a DEA problem.
我连襟  他知道房车的事了
My brother-in-law, he knows about the RV.
什么房车
What RV?
我们的房车
Our RV,
制冰毒的那个
the one which contains a meth lab,
里面到处都是我的指纹
which is covered with my fingerprints.
想起来没
Ring a bell?
想起来了  他知道多少
Okay, what exactly does "Knows about" Mean?
他找到车了吗  搜查了吗
Does he have it? Has he searched it?
没有  但他知道有这回事  他正在找
No, he knows it exists, and he's trying to find it.
他已经查到杰西了
He has linked it to Jesse,
找到房车只是时间问题
and it's only a matter of time before he tracks it down,
-所以  -所以赶紧把它处理掉
- So -So get rid of it.
你还不动手跟我说什么呢
What are you doing sitting here talking to me for?
最好就是  让平克曼去处理
Better yet, have Pinkman get rid of it.
懂吗  你最好别沾边
Right? You don't go near it.
不  听我说  我连襟他
No, no, listen, my brother-in-law,
正在监视杰西的房子  你明白吗
he is surveying Jesse's house. Do you understand?
就是说他可能已经监听电话并装了窃听器
So he might've tapped the phones or bugged his house.
那就实施计划A
Plan A, then.
出发  在调查局之前找到那车
Go. Get to it before the Feds do.
具体怎么处理
And do what exactly?
怎么...
I mean, what...
怎么...把房车那么大个的东西
The thing... The thing is the size of a...
处理掉
it's RV size.
我哪有本事让房车消失
I mean, where do I go to make an RV disappear?
我又不是大卫·科波菲尔
I'm not David Copperfield.
你问我我问谁  我又不是处理房车的
What do I look like, the RV disposal people?
-你没计划过这种情况怎么处理  -没
- Did you not plan for this contingency? - No.
那你下次先计划好
Well, next time, plan for it, would you?
星舰进取号还有自毁键呢
The Starship Enterprise had a self-destruct button.
-我的意思是  -够了  闭嘴
- I'm just saying. - Oh, Goss... shut up.
我的意思是  你看
I'm just saying, you know,
你摆弄工具这么在行
you're good with tools and all.
为什么不发明个水动力车呢
Why don't you invent a water-powered car, you know?
那样的话  就可以开着跑了
If you did that, you would be rolling in it.
套筒扳手递我
Socket wrench.
大号的
The big one.
怎么了
What?
你怕那些阿拉伯人
You scared of the Arabs?
你们疯啦  这车怎么能开出来
Are you out of your mind? Why is this out in the open?
你是谁啊
Who the hell are you?
他...他是海森堡
He's... He's Heisenberg.
能开吗  能开走吗
Is this drivable? Does it run?
能  我只是换个机油
Yeah, I was just changing the oil.
快换好
Well, finish it, quickly.
我们得把它擦干净开到沙漠里去
We'll wipe it clean and take it out to the desert.
过来帮忙
Come here and help me.
等等  为什么
Hold up. What's this about?
毒管局
The DEA,
毒品管制局
the Drug Enforcement Administration.
听说过吧
You've heard of them, haven't you?
我知道你听过
I know you have.
他们知道这辆房车的事了
They know all about this RV,
现在正在找它
and they're trying to find it right now.
我要它马上离开我的地盘
I want this off my property now.
不不不  我们得毁掉证据
No, no, no, no, no, we have got to destroy the evidence.
把它拆了烧掉  懂吗
We've got to rig this thing to burn. Do you understand?
不能在这  把这鬼东西弄走
Not here you don't. Just get it the hell out of here.
听我说  我需要你帮助
Now, listen to me. I need your help, okay?
要是我完了  我们全完蛋
If I go down, we all go down.
明白吗
Do you understand?
明白  我有更好的办法
All right, just... I know a better way.
我认识个人
I know a guy that'll wipe
能让它从此消失  不问来由
this off the planet, no questions asked.
打电话给他
Call him.
那杰西怎么办
Hey, what about Jesse?
凉拌
What about him?
喂  是我
Hey, it's me.
想听怪事吗
Wanna hear something weird?
听我说
Now, listen to me.
搞到地址  猴子  不管用什么手段
You get that address. Now, Badger, I don't care how!
一定要知道他把车弄到哪儿去
You find out where he's taking it!
这就对了
Oh, yeah.
打扰一下  你们吃好了吗
Excuse me. Are you leaving?
先生们  打扰一下
Excuse me, gentlemen.
座位是给消费的客人准备的
This booth is for paying customers.
辛西娅  没有关系
Cynthia, it's okay.
我来处理
I'll handle this.
有什么能效劳的吗
你心里清楚
等到日落
96  97  98  99  100
96, 97, 98, 99, 100.
要无法修复  明白吗
Beyond recovery, right?
-无法修复就是...  -我知道
- Now, beyond recovery means... - I get it.
无法修复
Beyond recovery.
-完全消失  没有证据  -别担心
- Obliterated, no evidence. - Hey, don't worry.
我们处理过之后
When we're through with it,
整个车就这么大一块了  怎样
it's going to be about yea big, okay?
然后用平板车运到长滩上
Then we flatbed it over to Long Beach,
再船运到太平洋对岸
ship it across the Pacific.
中国人会用它来做庭院里的家具
Chinese turn it into patio furniture,
你就放心吧
so... mind at ease.
你能再帮我个忙吗
Listen, can you do me a favor?
车没了我不太方便
I'm obviously going to need a ride.
能帮我叫辆车吗
Could you call a cab?
没问题  合作愉快
You got it. Pleasure doing business.
谢谢  我马上就来
Thank you. I'll be right behind you.
我只是...
I just need to...
-你在这里干什么  -你问我
- The hell you think you're doing? - Me?
它对我们两个来说都很重要
No, this is mine just as much as yours!
-你休想...  -糟了
- You don't get to just--  - Oh, God. Oh, God.
又怎么了
What?
他们来了
God, they're out--
怎么回事
What?
他在这里
He's here.
你说谁
Who's here?
别这样
Oh, no.
完了  这下完了
Oh, God. Oh, God.
是你引他过来的
You led him right to us.
该死
Shit.
平克曼先生  你还想加条拒捕的罪名吗
Mr. Pinkman, you want to add resisting arrest?
你没意见我一定照做  我可不在乎
We'll add it. No skin off my ass.
给你最后一次主动认罪的机会
Last chance to do it the easy way.
有搜查令吗
Got a warrant?
你是谁
Who are you?
你是谁啊  知道这辆房车的事吗
Who are you? What do you know about this RV?
我是这个场子的主人
Well, I'm the owner of this lot,
也就是说  你正非法入侵私人财产
which means you're trespassing on private property.
说到那辆旅行房车  我看它是被锁上了
As far as the RV goes, seems to me it's locked,
你却想破门而入
which means you're trying to break and enter,
所以我再问一遍  你是有搜查令还是怎么的
so I say again, you got a warrant?
如果我惹了麻烦  那才需要搜查令
Well, I don't need one if I've got probable cause,
"问题"先生
counselor.
无论车子停着或在干嘛
Probable cause usually relates to vehicles,
都很容易受损
is my understanding, you know,
这是我的理解  所以它才在这里
traffic stops and whatnot.
看到这些圆形塑胶的东西吗
See these round rubber things?
轮胎
Wheels.
这是一辆车
This is a vehicle.
这是一处住宅  一个居所
This is a domicile, a residence,
根据第四修正法案
and thus protected by the Fourth Amendment
可以拒绝非法搜查
from unlawful search and seizure.
朋友  你何不离开一下...
Look buddy, why don't you just go out and--
你有看到它开进这里吗
Did you see this drive in here?
你怎么知道它没坏
How do you know it runs?
你亲眼看到什么失德行为吗
Did you actually witness any wrongdoing?
在我看来  你出现在这里是为了...
It seems to me you're just out here...
就是到法庭上也没人会赞同这种行为
Don't see that holding up in a court of law.
是嘛
Oh, yeah?
过来看看
Well, look at these.
你觉得这像什么
What do those look like to you?
我觉得像是子弹干的
They sure look like bullet holes to me.
这个"住宅"曾经发生过交火事件
There was a firearm discharged inside of this "Domicile."
要打赌有几个法官会认为
Willing to bet there's a judge or two out there
这是意外  听好了
who'd see that as probable cause, but I'll tell you what.
你应该向阿尔伯克基市警方报案...
Why don't you call the Albuquerque police--
在你撕开胶布前
How could you have known that they were there
你怎么知道那里有弹孔
before you took off the tape?
你说什么
What?
在你撕开胶布前
How could you have known that they were there
你怎么知道那里有弹孔
before you took off the tape?
就这么说
Say it. Say it.
在你撕开胶布前
How could you have known that
你怎么知道那里有弹孔
they were there before you took off the tape?
里面说的没错
That's right.
显而易见  这种情况有很多种可能
Probable cause needs to be readily apparent.
里面有人
There's somebody in there.
...这里是私人住宅  我不想被骚扰
...private domicile and I won't be harassed.
听好了  平克曼
Yeah, I'll tell you what, Pinkman.
管它是不是意外  我给你三秒钟时间
Probable cause or no, I'll give you three seconds
滚出来
to get your ass out here.
1  2...
1, 2--
这里是我的私人住宅  别骚扰我
This is my own private domicile, and I will not be harassed.
衰人
Bitch.
你要搜查令嘛  简单
Fine. You want your warrant?
我会让弟兄们送来
I'll have my guys bring it out here
连同牢房一起送给你
and deliver it to you on a little satin pillow.
怎么样
How's that?
我已经等了很久了  再等会也无妨
I waited this long. Wait a little longer.
维姬
Hey, Vicky.
对  施拉德
Yeah, Schrader.
我找Merkert  谢谢
Give me Merkert, will you?
我想...
You know, I say--
直接撞他  怎么样
I say we just ram him. All right?
我们...
I mean, we, uh--
发动车子
we-- we start her up
直接撞烂他的破车
and just ram the shit out of his truck.
我们就能逃跑了
We make our escape. Right?
当然了  他会...
Yeah, he'd, uh--
他会一枪崩了我
he'd shoot me in the head.
他会崩了我
Yeah, he'd shoot me in the head.
我们该怎么办
So what do we do, man, huh?
我们...
What do we--
你想到什么了
What?
你是不是有办法了
Please tell me you got something.
对  是有个点子
Yeah, I got something.
是我
It's me.
我们需要你的帮助
We need your help.
是亨利·R·施拉德先生吗
Is this Mr. Henry R. Schrader?
对  你是哪位
Yeah. Who's this?
我是阿尔伯克基市警署的伊莲·坦纳警官
Sir, this is Officer Elaine Tanner with the Albuquerque Police.
玛丽·施拉德是你的妻子吗
Is your wife Marie Schrader?
是的  怎么了
Yes, why?
我很遗憾地通知你
I'm sorry to inform you that
你妻子发生了汽车事故
your wife's been in an automobile accident.
她正被送往Los Ranchos医疗中心
She's being airlifted to Los Ranchos Medical Center
即将抵达
and should be arriving there shortly.
她怎么样  情况如何
How is she? What's her condition?
我并不是...
I don't, um...
我不知道她的最新情况
have the most current information, sir,
希望你尽快前往那里
but I think you might want to get there as soon as possible.
你得给我加钱了
You're going to have to start paying me more.
-玛丽  -我刚到家
- Marie? - I'm just checking in.
我打来问问
I'd love to have some idea
要不要我准备晚餐
of whether I should cook dinner or not.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
我很好  怎么了
Yeah. Why?
汉克  发生什么了
Hank? What's up?
我早就告诉过你们
你们不能杀沃尔特·怀特
除非我跟他的交易结束了
我们等很久了
失去耐性了
你们不得不继续等着
这是命令
由不得你们
告诉我  为什么急着要杀怀特
他确实背叛了你们的堂兄屠库
但他不是杀人凶手
扣动扳机的
会不会另有其人
毒管局的探员
波尔沙说毒管局是禁区
北部边境是我的领地
那是我说的
而出于对波尔沙的尊敬...
这次我同意对毒管局动手
那位探员名叫
汉克·施拉德
希望他的死能慰藉你们